https://www.winwithp1ag.com/privacypolicy

CONTACT US
Player One Amusement Group Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy")
Effective date: July 1, 2017 At Player One Amusement Group Inc. and its subsidiaries, affiliates and/or related entities ("P1AG" or "our" or "we" or "us"), we share your concerns about privacy and the protection of your Personal Information. This Privacy Policy describes the steps we have taken and our practices regarding the protection of your personal information. Personal information is information about an identifiable individual. (the "Personal Information").
Our Privacy Policy allows you to reveal only such Personal Information as you wish. Our Privacy Policy also allows you to access, modify or entirely delete the Personal Information which you have provided to us.
If you have not already done so, we encourage you to familiarize yourself with this Privacy Policy before using P1AG websites and/or mobile applications (collectively the "Websites"). The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform our visitors, guests, business customer representatives and other individuals with whom we deal ("you" and "your") how we collect, use, disclose and protect your Personal Information. This Privacy Policy applies to our collection, use, disclosure and protection of your Personal Information in Canada.
If you are providing personal information to us through our Websites, your use of our Websites is governed by the Terms of Use (www.WinWithP1AG.com/Terms) of our Websites.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or about our practices with respect to Personal Information, or if you wish us to stop communicating with you, or if you wish us to delete your Personal Information from our database, please notify us:
• by email at privacy@Cineplex.com • telephone us at 1-877-323-6645 • or by mail at: Player One Amusement Group Inc. c/o Cineplex Entertainment LP 1303 Yonge Street
Toronto, ON M4T 2Y9
Attn: Chief Privacy Officer
Personal Information We Collect P1AG and its employees, agents, contractors, service providers, partners and representatives may collect Personal Information under certain circumstances, such as:
• Contact Information (e.g. name, address, telephone number or e-mail address); • Credit or Debit Card Information (e.g. when purchasing products or services); • Information relevant to a particular service you request (e.g. your company information); • Survey Responses (e.g. when you provide your name in order to take advantage of various benefits for participating in a survey, or when you consent to us contacting you about your comments and feedback); • Preferences and other Personal Information provided by you on our Websites (e.g. including but not limited to products you are interested in, purchase history, company information); • Credit Card and other information provided for the purchase of services or products (e.g. your name, your credit card number, expiry date and 3-digit CVS code). • Job Applications (e.g. such information as you provide to us when you apply for a job: (i) by sending us a resume; (ii) by submitting a job application on our Websites; or (iii) by submitting a job application through a third party Websites.
Use of Your Personal Information We collect and use Personal Information for a number of purposes:
• Purchases: Personal contact and credit/debit card information will be used by P1AG to process your purchases. In these cases, credit/debit card information is only used for the purposes required to process and complete the transaction and/or service requested by you, and is only retained in transaction records required for internal management and auditing purposes or as otherwise required by law, unless you are informed otherwise or you provide your consent.
• Administration: Also, your name, address and telephone number may be collected and used by P1AG for audit verification purposes. P1AG monitors its premises, electronically and otherwise, for crime deterrence and detection purposes, to which you implicitly consent when you visit our premises. In the event of accident or theft, P1AG may collect, use and disclose information related to the incident or theft as required for operational, insurance, legal or other necessary purposes.
• Contests/Benefits: P1AG may run contests, in locations, with our various business partners and through our Websites. We require your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address (for online entries) and we may also require proof of your age for the purposes of determining eligibility, prize notification and fulfilment and related purposes in connection with the contest. Contact information may be required to administer other benefits.
• Surveys: P1AG will occasionally conduct surveys and market research, in locations, by telephone, in person or on our Websites. These surveys and market research may ask you about your preferences, your region of residence or personal biographical or other information that may assist P1AG in understanding the preferences of its customers and guests. Your participation in such surveys or market research is entirely voluntary and, in some cases, you may be able to participate anonymously. Your contact information, including your name, address, telephone number and/or other Personal Information may be required: (1) to permit you to enjoy bonuses or benefits which may be available to survey or market research participants (in which case your contact information will only be used for notification or fulfillment purposes); or (2) where you have provided your express consent to us contacting you to discuss comments that you made during our surveys and/or market research. Except as described in this Privacy Policy, survey and/or research responses are only used by P1AG on an aggregate basis. • Other Uses: We may also use Personal Information, where necessary, for: o establishing, maintaining and/or fulfilling relationships with our business partners, third-party vendors of products and/or services, as well as our corporate and business customers; o evaluating Job applications or resumes which are sent to us (either by mail, electronic mail, through our Websites, or via third party Websites which advertise or list job openings) all of which are forwarded to our Human Resources Department or the relevant theatre(s) for consideration; o conducting operating, administering and otherwise managing our business, to satisfy legal, regulatory, security, audit, financial and processing requirements, or as otherwise permitted or required by law.
Disclosure of Personal Information Personal information collected by P1AG is not disclosed to other parties, except as follows:
We may share your Personal Information with outside parties who sponsor sweepstakes or other promotions, whether on our Websites or otherwise. However, we will not share your Personal Information with these parties except in accordance with this Privacy Policy. From time to time, P1AG contracts with third parties, such as other companies, individuals, contractors, and/or other entities, without limitation, to perform functions on our behalf. For instance, we may use such third parties to host message boards, user forums or webpages, to develop software applications and create and maintain databases, or send and receive communications on our behalf. Your Personal Information may be disclosed to such third party companies, individuals, contractors and/or other entities, without limitation, in the course of P1AG's business operations. All P1AG employees, servants, agents, contractors, representatives and/or partners who have access to your Personal Information are required to protect the information in a manner that is consistent with this and any other P1AG Privacy Policy, other policy and/or procedure, in effect from time to time.
Your Personal Information may be disclosed to our parent, subsidiary, affiliated and/or related corporations or entities, or to their employees, agents, contractors, representatives, servants, legal counsel and/or accountants without limitation, for operational, management and administrative purposes, as well as internal audit, legal, regulatory, security, insurance, financial, processing and other purposes, or as otherwise permitted or required by law. Personal information may also be transferred to certain other entities, whether subsidiary, related or affiliated entitles to P1AG or otherwise, where such entities provide administrative, management, operational, processing, support or other services to us, in which case we take steps to ensure that your Personal Information is protected and not used or disclosed for any purpose except: (i) as directed by P1AG; (ii) as permitted by this Privacy Policy; (iii) for which you are deemed to consent under the terms of this Privacy Policy; and/or (iv) as permitted or required by law.
In addition, P1AG may transfer Personal Information to outside agents, contractors, service providers or mandataries which perform services on our behalf (e.g. vendors’ fulfilment houses, survey, market research and contest service providers etc., in which case we use contractual or other means to ensure that your Personal Information is protected and not used or disclosed for any purpose except: (i) as directed by P1AG; (ii) as permitted by this Privacy Policy; (iii) for which you are deemed to consent under the terms of this Privacy Policy; and/or (iv) as permitted or required by law.
Your Personal Information may be used by P1AG and disclosed to parties connected with the contemplated or actual financing, insuring, sale, assignment or other disposal of all or part of P1AG's business or assets, including for the purposes of permitting such parties to determine whether to proceed or continue with such transaction or business relationship, to fulfill reporting, audit, legal and/or other requirements or, in the case of sale or assignment, the use and disclosure by those parties for substantially the same purposes as described in this Privacy Policy.
P1AG may also disclose Personal Information as necessary to meet legal, audit, regulatory, insurance, security or other requirements. P1AG does not disclose your Personal Information except: (i) as permitted by this Privacy Policy; (ii) for which you are deemed to consent under the terms of this Privacy Policy; and/or (iii) as permitted or required by law.
"WinWithP1AG.com" and the Internet The Websites have primary worldwide web address(es) (also known as the "uniform resource locator" or "URL") and consists of various webpages, which are owned and/or operated by P1AG and which are collectively known as "WinWithP1AG.com". The Websites consist of all content thereon and all other domain names, worldwide web addresses, uniform resource locators, URL’s and webpages which are solely owned and/or operated by P1AG, and which link or otherwise connect to the Websites. On the Websites, visitors may register to receive customized information, enter contests, participate in polls or surveys or purchase products and/or services. P1AG does not collect Personal Information about you unless you choose to provide us with such information in order to purchase a service or product, or participate in the WinWithP1AG.com online community and for which the provision of such Personal Information is necessary or reasonable.Regarding External Links: As a convenience to you and other visitors to the Websites, the Websites contains links to a number of third party Websites or third party webpages. These third party Websites and webpages are not owned or controlled by P1AG and this Privacy Policy does not apply to such Websites or webpages. Should you decide to navigate to any Websites or webpage external to the Websites, you do so entirely at your own risk. The content on third party Websites or webpages, as well as any external links on this Websites, is not investigated, assured, guaranteed, verified, monitored, recommended or endorsed by P1AG. P1AG provides these links merely as a convenience to you and to other visitors to this Websites, and the inclusion of such links does not imply that we endorse or recommend such Websites or webpages. We specifically disclaim any liability, obligation or responsibility whatsoever for the content or use of such third party Websites or webpages.Please note that the online purchase of product is conducted through such a third party Websites, and you should refer to the privacy policy, terms of use and other conditions applicable to the use of such Websites.We use information which you provide to us on the Websites to facilitate your registration, to understand the identity of our customers and/or guests and the nature of their preferences, to improve the content of the Websites, to customize the content and/or layout of our webpages for each visitor based on the information provided to us, to send you periodic newsletters and mailings that you request, to process your purchases and to conduct surveys, polls and contests. P1AG does not disclose Personal Information contained in our subscriber database to any third parties except: (i) as permitted by this Privacy Policy; (ii) for which you are deemed to consent under the terms of this Privacy Policy; and/or (iii) as permitted or required by law.Individuals who provide us with their telephone numbers online will only be telephoned by us with respect to orders, contests or other products or services that they have requested online. If you make inquiries of P1AG directly by e-mail, or through our Websites, these inquiries are forwarded to the relevant department and are not used for other purposes (without your consent), or stored (other than maintaining a record of our correspondence with you).
Unsubscribe / Deletion Requests E-Mail Receiving e-mail from us is optional when you register. If you initially choose to receive e-mail from us, but subsequently choose not to receive e-mail from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions on the Websites, in our e-mail or contact us as indicated at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Mail If you provide us with your mailing address, you may receive periodic mailings from us, or our business partners, with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mail from us, please change your preferences on the Websites, or contact us as indicated at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Online Profile When you register on our Websites, make purchases, enter contests, respond to surveys, or otherwise participate in our online community, our servers may store your Personal Information, contact particulars or other information in order to facilitate site login, the automatic completion of forms and otherwise for your convenience. If you prefer that we not store such information on our servers, you may select the appropriate option on the Websites (if that option is available) or you may contact us as indicated at the beginning of this Privacy Policy. Information Storage The nature of the internet is such that it passively and automatically collects certain information about each individual’s use of the internet. This information may be associated with an individual’s Internet Protocol ("IP") address. This is a unique internet "address" which is assigned to all internet users by their Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). Our server logs record statistical information, such as visitors' IP addresses, type of operating systems, time and duration of visit, webpages requested, as well as identifying categories of visitors by items such as domains and browser types. P1AG only uses these statistics on an aggregate basis in order for us to improve our Websites. Cookies Our Websites makes use of both "sessional" and "persistent" cookies. Cookies are small text files offered to your computer by Web servers in order to keep track of your browser settings as you navigate the site. Persistent cookies are stored on your hard drive. Sessional cookies are stored in temporary (cache) memory and are deleted when you shut down your browser or turn off your computer. We use cookies to store your preferences, record session information such as language preferences, record user-specific information on what pages you access or visit, develop information about your preferences and interests, alert you to areas that we think might be of interest to you when you return to our site, record past activity in order to provide better service when you return to our site, help rotate banner advertising so as to ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, and customize Websites content based on your browser type or other information you provide. For each visit to our Websites, cookies may be used by our server to recognize you where you have indicated your preference to be automatically logged in. You may disable cookies using your browser's settings. Please consult your browser's help function for information on how to disable cookies. Note that if you disable cookies, certain features of our Websites will not function to their fullest potential. To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, P1AG or its service providers place ads on our webpages. As a result of your visit to our site, or by clicking on these ads, we may collect passive information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. On our Websites we store subscriber and password information in a secure manner not accessible to Web browsers, behind password protection, or off-line. We endeavor to use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our Websites.
Your Consent Consent to the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information may be given in various ways. Consent may be express (e.g. orally, electronically or on a form you may sign describing the intended uses and disclosures of Personal Information) or implied (e.g. when you provide information necessary for a service you have requested (such as providing us with your name, phone number and/or email for use by our lost and found services), or in some circumstances where notice has been provided to you about our intentions with respect to your Personal Information and you have not withdrawn your consent for an identified purpose, such as by using an "opt-out" option. Consent may be given by your authorized representative (such as a legal guardian, person having a power of attorney or a mandatary). By providing us with Personal Information, we will deem you to understand this Privacy Policy, and we will deem you to consent to our collection, use and disclosure of such Personal Information for the purposes identified or described in this Privacy Policy, if applicable, or otherwise at the time of collection. You may withdraw your consent to our collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information at any time, subject to contractual and legal restrictions and reasonable notice. Note that if you withdraw your consent to certain uses of your Personal Information, we may no longer be able to provide you with certain of our products or services.P1AG does not disclose your Personal Information except: (i) as permitted by this Privacy Policy; (ii) for which you are deemed to consent under the terms of this Privacy Policy; and/or (iii) as permitted or required by law. However, P1AG may be required or permitted under statute, regulation or as otherwise at law or in equity to collect, use or disclose Personal Information without your consent (for example, in response to a court order or subpoena, or to comply with local or federal regulations, or to collect a debt owed to us).
Security We protect your Personal Information using physical, electronic or procedural security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information in our custody or control, including safeguards to protect Personal Information against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, or modification. P1AG and its employees, servants, agents, contractors, legal, accounting or other service providers, partners, representatives and mandataries who require access to your Personal Information in order to fulfill their job requirements will have access to your Personal Information. You transmit or provide all Personal Information entirely at your own risk.
Consent to Transfer P1AG's Websites are operated on equipment located in Canada. If you are located in the United States of America, European Union or elsewhere outside Canada, please be aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to Canada. By visiting WinWithP1AG.com, purchasing our products or services, participating in our online community and/or providing us with your Personal Information, you consent to this transfer. Regardless of your location, we shall protect your Personal Information using physical, electronic or procedural security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information in our custody or control, including safeguards to protect Personal Information against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, or modification. Please note that the Personal Information which you provide to us will be held and used in accordance with such Canadian federal or provincial laws as exist from time to time, and as are applicable.
Note to Parents/Children's Privacy Protecting children's privacy is important to us. For that reason, we do not collect information on our Websites from those children we actually know are under 13 years of age. In addition, no part of our Websites are targeted to attract anyone under 13 years of age. We request that children under 13 years of age do not disclose or provide any Personal Information. If we discover such information, we will delete the child's Personal Information from our records. If for any reason we believe a user may be under the age of 13 we reserve the right to request proof of age of such user. If such proof is not provided, or if it is discovered a user is under the age of 13 all Personal Information of that user shall be deleted from our servers and associated systems and we reserve the right to limit and/or ban such user from our Websites. P1AG also believes that parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools, available from online services and software manufacturers, to help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools may also prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other Personal Information without parental permission. For additional information about parental control tools, please visit http://www.icra.org/_en/parents.
Policy ChangesThis Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time as P1AG deems necessary or advisable in its sole discretion. If we materially change our privacy practices, we shall notify you of such changes on our Websites; if necessary, we shall also update our Privacy Policy as it appears on our Websites. If our information practices change such that your privacy may be materially affected, we shall notify you of such changes on our Websites; if necessary, we shall also update our Privacy Policy as it appears on our Websites. You will continue to have the ability to opt out of new non-essential uses or disclosures. If you are concerned with how your Personal Information is used, we encourage you to bookmark this site and to periodically review our Privacy Policy, or contact us as described below to obtain a current copy of our Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy was last updated on July 1, 2017.
Access, Correction and Contacting UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or about our practices with respect to Personal Information, or if you wish us to stop communicating with you, or if you wish us to delete your Personal Information from our database, please notify us:
• by email at privacy@Cineplex.com • telephone us at 1-877-323-6645 • or by mail at: Player One Amusement Group Inc. c/o Cineplex Entertainment LP 1303 Yonge Street
Toronto, ON M4T 2Y9
Attn: Chief Privacy Officer
Please clearly indicate the information that you wish to review or have changed. We will to reply to your request as soon as reasonably possible.© 2017 Player One Amusement Group Inc.
ABOUT PLAYER ONE
Whatever your game, our team can help you win. With 25 offices across North America, and over 550 staff, we’re the one player that can offer you a Total Solution. Take your game to the next level. Contact Us
Connect with Player One Amusement Group:
ABOUT PLAYER ONE
Whatever your game, our team can help you win. With 25 offices across North America, and over 550 staff, we’re the one player that can offer you a Total Solution. Take your game to the next level. Contact Us
Connect with Player One Amusement Group:
